Hello, my friends.
And welcome to exercise number 40.
We are asked to implement the link at list in Java and create three notes.
So for that, we have learned about how to implement it in Java A..
But we need to show you the code, how it works with that idea.
OK, so we have learned deeply in C, and the exercises would cover a big part of Java.
So this course is mixing and showing you the code in both C and Java.
If you are a C program and or a Java programmer, so you can go with this course without any problem.
OK.
So.
We start.
I will delete this class and make a class new class Java class here called linkage list.
This class link and list, it contains a class called aesthetic class static class.
This is as a structure and as you c language.
I will create an inner class called not OK.
This no.
This in our class is made static so that the main can access it.
And later, I will make a link list of of by end and a pointer to the No.
OK, I will create a constructor here.
This is the constructor and the and here I refer to the data equal today and the next equal to none.
OK.
It's very simple.
This is the constructor.
Now.
Here.
In the linked list class, I will create a new object from this class called had.
This would be have of their list.
OK.
Till now, we have created a class called Not.
And we have created an object from it called heÉp.
OK, now let's move to the method, the main method that we need to create to run it and create the
three no public static void main.
And I will make strange args.
The keys are in Java.
OK.
Let's start with empty list.
Empty list.
Linked list, I will create an object from linkage list.
Linked list equal to new link this.
Link, at least now Dot had this is the hat I'm referencing to air new nod.
So what I am specifying in the note, I need to pass and an end date.
OK, so look at here, guys link list Dot had.
This is the head.
This is the first one.
It will make and you nod.
But what it will contain, it will contain data.
So what is the number it would be like number one?
This is that data that is contained in the first note.
Now, in order to make a second and third, not now, it would be not second
equal to new nod, and we specify using this constructor.
What is the data is it was good to know if I need to create the third node third, not in the same way.
Equal, equal to new node of diversity of data.
Three.
OK.
This is very simple.
Three nodes have been allocated dynamically.
We have references to these three blocks as head second and third.
OK.
So I want from you to think about this as this demonstration.
So as I told you, think about this, I am making Lincoln List that contains.
The data as end.
So the first one is called, had this is the had the first known, it contains no one as data and the
reference.
There is no difference here.
OK, so it didn't create any difference till now.
The second, not we just create the notes, OK?
The second note contains number two and the third nod is containing number three.
OK.
This is the code second.
This is called third, not OK.
I need from you to understand these concepts because they are very important, and you may ask deeply
what this means.
Okay, so this is the head we just specified by linkage list that had equal to Newnan.
We have created this head here linked list that had I'm accessing the class that had gay.
I'm specifying as the main node the main had would be equal to one.
OK, now our mission is to make that reference.
So how to make the reference, how to make the linking, how to allow this to be referencing to another
and not.
OK.
This will return at this with reference to none.
This to reference the three and one reference to two with which is the next note.
So how to do this?
How to make this link?
So we start.
This is the linking.
Stacked
list, linked list, the tab dot next.
I am referencing the first one is the next of the head would be the second.
No.
I am linking the first with the second.
Now, in order to link the second with the third, I am just make second, not the next I am accessing
now.
So you see guys here, we have seen that, that that we create that data inside.
Now, in order to make the reference and the link, I will make here.
Second, not an equal to the third.
Not OK.
This is that link.
Now, next of then, the second node refers to the third.
So all the three nodes are linked.
OK.
This is how we make that data structure link at least inside Java and create that the three nodes.
And we have to link them to each other in the next videos.
We are going to print their list and make operation on it.